oh we say we were going to stop they
wanted to see the ruins yeah but should
we wake them up I know you know what
let's do on our way back to the airport
we can catch him you know we yeah I'm
probably
not and how did you two meet we met
about 18 years ago we kind of sort of
fell in
love and a decade later we ran into each
other no no no you wrote a book and I
read about it and went to look for it
that's pretty romantic if we're meeting
for the first time today on a train
would you start talking to me would you
ask me to get up the train with you of
course well this place is so full of
thousands of years of myth and tragedy
and I thought something tragic was going
to happen still there still
there
G you never stop UGL girls I don't augle
girls I'm make a love to them with my
eyes oh wow I'm stuck with an American
Teenager where's my team where's my team
I feel close to you yeah but sometimes I
don't know I feel like you're breathing
helium and I'm breathing oxygen what
makes you say
that I wanted you to say something
romantic in you okay you are the mayor
of crazy town do you know that you
[Music]
are this is how people start breaking up
oh my God I assure you that guy you
vaguely remember the sweet romantic one
that you met on a
train that is
me why am I finding myself so attracted
to this woman
[Music]