[Music]
what do you do you're not an engineer
you're not a designer
you can't put a hammer to a nail I built
the circuit board the graphical
interface was stolen
so how come ten times in a day I read
Steve Jobs as a genius what do you do
musicians play their instruments I play
the orchestra here you've been worse
than usual this morning I didn't think
that was possible it's a system error
fix it fix it yeah we're not a pit crew
at Daytona this can't be fixed in
seconds you didn't have seconds you had
three weeks the universe was created in
the third of that time well someday
you'll have to tell us how you did it
I'm begging you to manage expectations
out there you see how this reminds you
of a friendly face it's warm and it's
playful and inviting and it needs to say
hello if you keep alienating people for
no reason there will be no one left for
it to say hello to your Apple stock was
worth 441 million dollars well your
daughter
and her mother are on welfare she's not
my daughter you must be able to see that
she looks like you
you're issuing contradictory
instructions you're insubordinate you
make people miserable even if that
weren't true doesn't sound that
diabolical to me
we've spoken to the fire marshal in the
building manager they're gonna come in
and tell everyone to leave if a fire
causes a stampede to the unmarked exits
it'll have been well worth it for those
who survived the port police you're no
longer necessary to this company
I sent Mirage and invented the future
because artists lead and hacks ask for
show of hands you're gonna anything are
you you're being ridiculous
I'm gonna sit center court and watch you
do it yourself make you everything all
right with Lisa fix it
you