[Music]
I need to do something substantial in
order to get the attention of the club's
why because they're exclusive and fun
and they lead to a better life
[Music]
people want to go on the internet and
check out their friends so why not build
a website that offers that friends
pictures profiles I'm talking about
taking the entire social experience of
college and putting it online so I've
got 2,200 hits within two hours thousand
22,000 this idea is potentially worth
millions of dollars
millions install our website they're
saying we stole the Facebook I know what
it said so did we
you know it's cool a billion down you're
going to get left behind it's moving
faster than any of us never get behind
it's sued him in federal court I can't
wait to stand over your shoulder in what
you write is it if you guys were
the inventors of Facebook that to
Facebook is there anything that you need
to tell me your actions could have
permanently destroyed everything I've
been working greed
[Music]
you're being accused of intentionally
breaching security violating copyrights
violating individual privacy
your best friend is suing you for six
hundred million dollars as for the
charges I believe I deserve some
recognition from this board I'm sorry
yes I don't understand which part
[Music]